mcmelectronics.com 2012-10-11

# MCM Electronics | Help Center - Privacy Policy

MCM respects your right to privacy. We developed this Privacy Statement to inform you about our practices. Questions regarding this Privacy Statement should be directed to [talk@mcmelectronics.com](mailto:talk@mcmelectronics.com?subject=Privacy%20Statement%20Questions).

* ## Overview

Privacy is a concern to most Internet users. MCM is acutely aware of, and sensitive to, the privacy concerns of our customers. We assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. If you are registering to use the site you will be asked to provide certain information. We are asking for this information solely for the purpose of providing the services offered and authenticating your identity when you login.

Back to top
* ## Privacy Policy Enforcement

If you feel that MCM is violating this Privacy Statement, please contact us at [talk@mcmelectronics.com](mailto:talk@mcmelectronics.com).

Back to top
* ## Use of Postal Addresses

We occasionally make the names and postal addresses of our customers available to highly screened companies that offer products and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive these third-party offers, please let us know by contacting MCM at 1-800-543-4330.

Back to top
* ## Traffic Data

We collect click-stream data such as referring URL, browser and platform, time of visit, pages visited and searches performed. These statistics are used to help us improve the performance of our website and better serve our customers. We analyze this data to establish trends and help us improve your online experience.

Aggregated traffic data may be shared with potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners for demographic purposes. When used in this aggregated form no one will be able to identify or contact you.

Back to top
* ## Use of E-mail Addresses

When you register on MCMEletronics.com, you may receive email promotions from MCM. To unsubscribe from these emails, MCM will contain unsubscribe information so that you may opt-out of future e-mails. E-mails that confirm business transactions will always be sent to you.

Back to top
* ## Use of Cookies

A "cookie" is a text file that our website sends to your browser to store your preferences. Cookies allow our website to "remember" information about your preferences either until you exit your current browser window (if the cookie is temporary) or until you disable or delete the cookie. Many users prefer to use cookies to help them navigate a website as seamlessly as possible. We use "cookies" to enhance your experience on our site.

You should be aware that cookies contain no more information than you volunteer, and they are not able to "invade" your hard drive and return to the sender with personal or other information from your computer. If you choose not to accept a cookie, you are still welcome at our website, however we will not be able to accept online orders.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Back to top
* ## Sending You Responses and Updates

We generally respond to any e-mail questions, requests for service or information, and other inquiries we receive. We may also retain this correspondence to improve our products, services and website. Frequently we retain contact information so that we can send individuals updates or other important information about our services and products.

Back to top
* ## Surveys

From time-to-time we may request information via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you always have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve this website, and to improve our customer service and product offerings.

Back to top
* ## Security

Find out how we maintain a high level of security on our site.

Back to top
* ## Terms of Use

The MCM website may contain links to third-party sites. The linked sites are not under the control of MCM, and MCM is not responsible for the contents of any linked site, any link contained in a linked site, any changes or updates to such linked sites, or any transmission from any linked site. MCM is providing these links to third-party sites only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by MCM of the site.

Back to top
* ## License and Site Access

MCM grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of this site and not to download (other than page caching) or modify it, or any portion of it, except with express written consent of MCM. This license does not include any resale or commercial use of this site or its contents; any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or prices; any derivative use of this site or its contents; any downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of another merchant; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent of MCM.

You are granted a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to the home page of mcmelectronics.com so long as the link does not portray MCM, its parent company, or their products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise offensive matter. You may not use any MCM logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without express written permission.

Back to top
* ## Copyright

The site and the content within the site are the property of MCM Electronics or its suppliers and are protected by United States copyright laws and international treaty provisions. The compilation, organization and display of the content as well as all software and inventions used on and in connection with this Site are the exclusive property of MCM. These materials may not be copied or redistributed for any for any purposes without prior written permission from MCM. Copyright © 2005© by MCM, Dayton, OH 45459.

Back to top
* ## Trademark Information

MCM, MCM Electronics, SPC Technology, Stellar Labs, Defender Security, Multicomp and Tenma are registered trademarks of Premier Farnell PLC. MCM's i-Tracker and ProductFind trademarks are the sole and exclusive property of Premier Farnell PLC. All other registered and / or unregistered trademarks displayed on this site constitute the intellectual property of their respective holders.

Back to top
